http://www.masystem.com/Contact/Data-protection-policy

.
MA-system AB's data protection policy
MA-system AB, company reg. no. 556199-7494 (hereinafter referred to as MA-system), with its head office at Porfyrvägen 14, 224 78 Lund, Sweden, protects your personal privacy. This data protection policy explains how MA-system collects and uses personal data. If you have any questions about privacy and data protection, please contact us at info@masystem.se
When you contact us, for example to buy a product or service from us, you accept our data protection policy and agree to our processing of your personal data. You also agree to MA-system using electronic communication channels to send information to you.
To be able to offer you our services and products, we need to process your personal data as described below. We do this with the utmost consideration given to your privacy.
What information do we collect?
Collection and use of data
This data protection policy covers data collected online and offline, including personal data that we may collect through multiple channels such as websites, social media, phone or email contact, and at events/trade expos. We may combine personal data collected in one way (for example a website) with personal data collected another way (e.g. trade expos, customer meetings).
Information that you provide to us: You can directly or indirectly provide us with information about you and your company in a number of different ways, such as when you inquire about or purchase a product or service we sell, register for our newsletter, interact with our social media, or contact us by email, letter or phone. Such information can include:
Personal and contact details – name, date of birth, personal identity number, billing and delivery address, email address, mobile phone number, position in the company, qualifications, etc.
Payment information – billing information, bank account information, etc.
Information we collect about you: When you come in contact with us, we may collect information such as the following (note that we do not necessarily always collect the data indicated below):
Personal and contact details such as name, date of birth, personal identity number, billing and delivery address, email address, mobile phone number, photo, position in the company, employee number, and qualifications.
Information about products/services – details about the products and services you purchased/showed interest in purchasing.
Financial information – any credits, debts or negative payment history.
Historical information – previous courses taken, purchases, payment and credit history
Device information – for example IP address, language settings, browser settings, time zone, operating system, platform and screen resolution
Geographical information – your geographical location
The information you provide us, the information we collect about you, the information about products and services, and the financial information are generally necessary to be able to enter into a contractual relationship with us, while the other information we collect is generally necessary for other purposes, as described below.
What do we do with the information?
We provide, perform and improve our services. All data is used to provide, perform and improve our services.
Who might we share the information with?
In order to fulfil our commitments to our customers and other stakeholders, we may transfer or share the information with third parties, like suppliers or subcontractors, authorised dealers and distributors, or service providers. We take all reasonable legal, technical and organisational measures to ensure that the data is handled securely and with an adequate level of protection when transferring to or sharing with third parties. All processing of personal data is carried out in accordance with the latest version of the General Data Protection Regulation.
Authorities. We may provide necessary information to the relevant authorities if we are required to do so by law or if you have agreed to this.
What we will NOT do with the data.  MA-system will not sell the collected information to any third party.
Where do we process your personal data?
MA-system processes the data within the EU/EEA. The company takes all reasonable legal, technical and organisational measures to ensure that the data is handled securely and with an adequate level of protection.
How long do we save the data?
We save data as long as necessary to fulfil the purpose for which the data was collected or to perform our undertaking, and as long as required by statutory storage times, particularly as regards reporting requirements.
Your rights to access, correction and deletion
Right to have access to your data. You have the right to request a copy of the information that MA-system has about you and to verify this information.
Right to correction. You have the right to request correction of information about you that is incorrect or incomplete.
Right to be deleted (“right to be forgotten”). You have the right to request the deletion of your personal data in cases where the data is no longer required for the purpose it was collected. However, there may be legal obligations that prevent us from immediately deleting parts of the data. These obligations may come from accounting and tax legislation. In such cases, we block the data we are obliged to save from use for purposes other than fulfilling such legal obligations.
Cookies and similar technologies.
MA-system uses cookies on its website to provide a user-friendly online experience.
Contact us
If you have any questions about data protection, please contact us at info@masystem.se
The data protection policy was last updated 26 april 2018.
Contact
Data protection policy
Cookies
About MA-system
The MA-system company group consist of MA-system Consulting and MA-system Utbildning. Thus, MA-system offer services and products ranging from strategic profitability analysis and Supply Chain Control systems to operational improvements of processes and education of staff.
Contact
MA-system AB
Porfyrvägen 14
SE-224 78 LUND
info@masystem.com
+46 46-32 90 00
Data protection policy
Cookies
